Today, we'll learn about Christopher Columbus, the heroic explorer who discovered America and proved the Earth was wrong.
I'm really sorry, Ms. Dazzle, but Columbus never set foot in America.
Of all the modern-day countries Columbus made it to, like Cuba, Haiti, and the Dominican Republic, none of them were in the United States.
Okay, fine. Then Columbus discovered Haiti in the Dominican Republic.
Sure he did, if you don't count the quarter million Taino people that lived there already.
The Taino treated Columbus and his crew with the utmost hospitality.
Hug?
We need the reinforcements!
Columbus repaid their kindness by returning with 17 ships and 1,200 men so he could enslave the Taino and steal their gold.
There was only one problem. They didn't have any.
You!
Gold!
Now!
I want to help, but what is gold?
This infuriated Columbus, and soon, he and his crew...
I can't believe it!
I had no clue that Columbus was this cruel.
But after this, he must have gone on to do great things.
Nope.
This was literally all he did.
He didn't discover America, and he didn't prove the Earth was round.
He just bounced around the Caribbean, slaughtered a bunch of innocent people, and died thinking he had made it to India.
Hashtag...